ALEXIS QUINTUÑA

alexisiquintuna@gmail.com I (646) 730-3569

linkedin.com/in/alexis-quintuna | github.com/alexisquintuna | alexisquintuna.com

Passionate Full-Stack Software Developer, with a craving to use new technology and tools to elevate clients brand. Using my academic experience to build dynamic applications, in all aspects of the user experience and user interface.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- → Object-Oriented Programming: .Net | JavaScript
- ➤ Web Application Development: HTML | CSS | ASP.NET Core | Vue.js | React | Node.js | Express | TailWind | SquareSpace | Wordpress | WIX
- → Database Programming: ADO.NET | Table Design | E/R diagrams | MVC | MongoDB
- → **Development Tool & Techniques:** Agile | Unit Testing | Integration Testing | REST | Figma | Postman

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

- **TraingingGrounds** Contributed on a redesign project for a daycare, increasing target audience by 15% and reducing site production by close to 2 weeks.
- CatCrack Developed a landing page allowing users to view what CatCrack has to offer. Provided user satisfaction while delivering an exceptional user experience throughout the site. The user experience made the site gain an audience increase of over 300%
- **OPEN CITY -** Collaborated with a team to design and develop an application that allows users to plan adventures anywhere. Implemented agile methodologies to create the user login, search for landmarks in a city, and add them to the adventure card. The adventure card contains a travel route that includes all the landmarks inside. The full-stack web application was built with the help of VS2019 SSMS | .Net ADO.NET Vue.js
- **Genere Natus 2.0** Created and designed with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React as the library. Developed a landing page web app for a car club. Initially, what started as vanilla HTML and CSS, with tools I taught myself I went back and designed a new version of the site in Figma to then develop it using React to test my front-end abilities and the tools I self-taught myself. With the skills applied, I was able to generate 20% more user engagement on the site.

EDUCATION

Tech Elevator, Columbus, OH

SEPT 2022 – DEC 2022

Attended a 14-week full-stack coding boot camp learning how to create dynamic web-based software systems using .NET/C# providing 800+ hours of development education and application.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

The Roosevelt Coffeehouse, Columbus, OH

SEPT 2019 - PRESENT

Lead Barista

- Appointed and took the initiative to handle a coffee shop location by myself, handling over 100 transactions a day.
- Juggled different projects, roles, and event planning with relative ease. Adjusted to the company's needs for the day from the leader to manager to cashier, team player with motivation to see the company succeed.
- Took ownership of accomplishing new and different requests to enhance the shop's reputation and generate revenues. The store's reputation went up by 15% around Ohio by acquiring new clients to provide our coffee too which generated more than \$15,000 a year for the business.

Astra Studio, Columbus, OH

January 2023 - PRESENT

Contract

- Succeeded in merging into an unknown environment, quickly being able to connect, encourage, energize and diversify the team by bringing a different perspective and attitude towards obstacles.
- Secured, executed and completed 2 projects, receiving positive and encouraging feedback from clients and co-workers. Kept composure, able to mold and think quick on any scenario thrown at when dealing with both projects at once.
- Devoted to learn new tools and technologies like Wordpress, squarespace, and Wix to grow companies clientele, resulting the company now being able to bring 3x more clients an estimated value of over \$50,000+ annually.